crispytech.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy

Advertisement

We respect your privacy and we are fully committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at this site [Crispy Tech](http://www.crispytech.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

#### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

####  **E-mail Subscription**

If a user wishes to subscribe to Crispy Tech posts via e-mail _(powered by Feedburner)_ , we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We have respect for our user’s privacy and choice, so a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site uses cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Crispy Tech have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings or manually.

#### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our readers to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Advertisers

We may use outside ad companies to display ads on this Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). We work with these ad companies for now: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

####  **Contact Information**

If you have any suggestion or question regarding [Crispy Tech’s](http://www.crispytech.com/) privacy policy, please contact by filling up the [contact form](http://www.crispytech.com/contact/).

Advertisement
